export default [
  {
    title: "Welcome to the Agile Quiz",
    questionlist: [
      {
        question: "Who is responsible for prioritizing the product backlog?",
        answers: [
          "Product Owner",
          "Project Manager",
          "Lead Developer",
          "Tester"
        ],
        correct: 1
      },

      {
        question: "Which one of the following is not a Scrum role?",
        answers: ["Product Owner", "Scrum Master", "Product Manager", "Team"],
        correct: 3
      },
      {
        question: "Which one of the following is not a Scrum artifact?",
        answers: [
          "Product Backlog",
          "Story",
          "Sprint Backlog",
          "Burndown Chart"
        ],
        correct: 2
      },
      {
        question: "Which of the following meetings is not part of Scrum?",
        answers: [
          "Product Review Meeting",
          "Sprint Review Meeting",
          "Sprint Planning Meeting",
          "Sprint Retrospective Meeting"
        ],
        correct: 1
      },
      {
        question: "'Velocity' is a measure of ...",
        answers: [
          "Customer buy in",
          "Project Progress",
          "Executive Support",
          "Risk Mitigation"
        ],
        correct: 2
      },
      {
        question:
          "Name the meeting during which the team demonstrates to the product owner and any other interested parties what it was able to accomplish during the Sprint..",
        answers: [
          "Product Review Meeting",
          "Sprint Review Meeting",
          "Stakeholder Review Meeting",
          "Sprint Retrospective Meeting"
        ],
        correct: 2
      },
      {
        question: "The phases in an agile project are",
        answers: [
          "Inception, Conceptualization, Execution, Transition, Closure",
          "Inception, Design, Execution, Transition, Closure",
          "Due Diligence, Design, Execution, Verification, Closure",
          "Inception, Conceptualization, Execution, Verification, Closure"
        ],
        correct: 1
      },
      {
        question:
          "This phase contains activities that form the iterative and incremental development cycle.",
        answers: ["Development", "Inception", "Conceptualization", "Execution"],
        correct: 4
      },
      {
        question:
          "Is a style of programming in which three activities are tightly interwoven: coding, testing and design and ensures that no untested code makes it into the system...",
        answers: [
          "Joint Application Design",
          "Test Driven Development",
          "Continuous Integration and Testing",
          "Improvement Workshop"
        ],
        correct: 2
      },
      {
        question:
          "The metric used to measure Number of story points completed in a sprint/ iteration is:",
        answers: [
          "Sprint Burn Down",
          "Velocity",
          "Acceleration",
          "Business Velocity"
        ],
        correct: 2
      }
    ]
  }
];
